adzuna.co.uk 2016-04-14

# Privacy policy

This policy sets out how we use and protect information we collect about you when you use this website.

## Who we are

Adzuna is the trading name of Adhunter Ltd, a privately-owned UK company.

## What information we may hold about you

We may hold any information you provide to us including your e-mail address, user account details and information contained in your CV. We may also store details of your historic job searching preferences and behaviour.

## What we do with this information

We use this information to make your job search experience better. For example, we may use your work history to help identify the most relevant job recommendations for you. From time to time we may use your contact details to send you these job recommendations and other information relevant to your job search. By providing us with your contact details you consent to receiving such communications. You can opt out at any time by going to your account settings or by unsubscribing using the instructions contained in each communication.

## Marketing and third parties

From time to time we may share your information with third parties that we use to help us process data or who have directly relevant products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. This may include third parties who wish to contact you in relation to potential employment opportunities. If you would prefer not to be contacted by any third parties you can request this at any time by sending us a message using our [online contact form.](https://www.adzuna.co.uk/contact-us.html)

## How we safeguard your data

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

## Viewing and changing your personal information

You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information please write to us at the address given below. We may make a small charge for this service.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is saved on your computer by a website. Cookies are typically used on your subsequent visits to a website and they enable it to remember information about your preferences. Generally, cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. Included within the definition of cookies are Locally Stored Objects ("Flash Cookies"), and HTML5 Local Storage. More information about cookies can be found here: [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

Adzuna uses two types of cookie:

  1. Cookies set by us: we use these to improve your user experience, for example by saving your recent searches so you can access them again easily or by saving your password to automatically log you into your Adzuna account 
  2. Cookies set by third parties: these primarily enable us to track the performance of our website which helps us improve the service we provide (for example through Google Analytics which collects anonymous statistical data about pages visited) 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you decline cookies, you may lose functionality or features of the Adzuna website.

## Other websites

Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to another website then their privacy policy will apply.

## Changes to our privacy policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. This privacy policy was last updated on 10th of November 2015.

## How to contact us

You can get in touch with us via our [online contact form](https://www.adzuna.co.uk/contact-us.html), or alternatively you can write to us at our registered office:

> Adhunter Limited,  
> Second Floor, Alexander House,  
> 14-16 Peterborough Road, Fulham,  
> London SW6 3BN.
